financesumit.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy | Provide financial market information

You are welcome to visit and use http://financesumit.com/ in this privacy notice we declare to the visitor’s privacy promise.Without you agree, we will never put your personal data provided to any third person has nothing to do with this web site service.  
If you access this web site, you accept this privacy statement.The following text I stand for information collection and use of public.This website’s privacy statement will continue to improve, with the increase of standing service, we will update our privacy statement.  
You are always welcome to view this statement, and [ feedback ](http://financesumit.com/Contact%20us/)  
to us your opinion

1.the special attention of minors  
If you are under 18, you have no right to use the service, so we hope you will not provide any personal information to us.If you are under 18, you can only be accompanied by a parent or guardian to use the service.

2.Information collection and use  
When you register this website enterprise member in, we require you to provide relevant information in the form of filling in forms, such as your real name, position, address, telephone number, email address, your company’s services and product details such as brief explanation, as long as you are in this website to register and log in the server, we will be able to identify you and your enterprise information.We will be according to the statistical data to give us corporate membership classification, such as industry, product, enterprise property, so that targeted to provide new services to our corporate members and opportunities.We will inform you through your email address – these new services and opportunities.

3.Your trading behavior  
We track the IP address for the truthfulness of the identity and transaction identification, safety and other meet the requirements of the state.If we didn’t find any security issues, we will delete after 60 days we collected by the IP address.We also tracks throughout the page to access the data.Throughout the page to access the data are used to reflect the traffic, so that we can make plans for future growth (for example, increase the server).  
Because of your trading activity and other data, we will use these statistics to membership classification, so that targeted to provide new services to our members and opportunities.We’ll let you know by your email address to the new services and opportunities.

4.Open and sharing of information  
This website will publish enterprise users to submit business opportunities and product information, quotation, and other users can query the business opportunities, product information and quotation.We will not provide to any third party, sell, rent, share, and transaction user’s personal information;Unless the third party and this website to provide services, and in the service after the end of the third party will be banned from access, including its former, to be able to access all of these data may be deleted.When we are law enforcement or provide your information in accordance with government requirements we will disclose your information kindly

5.The use of cookies  
Cookies are small amounts of data, in case you do not refuse to accept cookies, cookies will be sent to your browser, and stored in your computer’s hard drive.We use cookies to the data store you visit our website, when you access or visit our website again, we can identify your identity, and through the analysis of data provide more better service for you.  
You have the right to accept or refuse to accept cookies.You can change the browser Settings to refuse to accept cookies, but we need to remind you, because you refuse to accept cookies, you might not be able to use depends on the part of cookies on our website

6\. Links to Other Sites  
Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

7\. Commitment  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Seeking Alpha’s Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

8\. Your Consent  
By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to Seeking Alpha’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
